Second down here's your body Williams has been great.
Oh my gosh the headbutt he's still going forward
What a run by job on Daisy's smashed more Sean Lattimore
There's press got to throw looking over the middle
CD land is back and he delivers on a first down catch
This commander's defense is a huge challenge
Scott
There is a flag as Marshawn Lattimore had the coverage
Whether it's a catch or interference he gets leverage on Lattimore
Defense number two
Now the balls a little bit under thrown Lattimore doesn't
get his head around but I really like the pass protection
that's what allows you to develop those plays
down the field and throw it up there for your
certainly
Talented receiver pickup,
but look at the protection you have that clean pocket
like that where you can just truly first and goal
It is with Williams about
Give it to Javante
Touchdown talus
Pull the guard Allen
Excuse me Tyler Smith
And Williams just reading the block
when Smith ends up in the end zone now
It's his stage as get a hand off to
cross game Mary who races up the middle
He's had a really good rookie year.
He had a fumble last week actually last two weeks
But and now it's Tress way to punt it away to Turpin
High spiraling booming kick Turpin lets it go
Wow Percy Butler toe tap walk the line and
the Cowboys will have it inside the one
What a pun 58 yards and personally Butler.
Maybe he did a little ballet back in the day
I mean walking along that line pretty hard to be undefeated,
but they found a way
Today Williams is in trouble.
He's gonna be dropped for safety.
I
Still haven't seen the signal,
but he did not get out and there it is
Doron Payne blew up the play two points for the commanders
Just an inside run.
They called us a duo run
Straight downhill the whole ball has to get over the goal
line and you can't even see it there with those bodies
Maybe from the overhead look
Williams pain breaking through on
on schoonmaker
Just can't get quite on what a play
obviously it's a great defensive play
But that's all sped up set up by that special teams
play Larry is oh as this special teams unit just on fire
Does it then do this hand off across key
merit sprinting up the middle and like a jet
Croskey Mary with a nice little one.
He picks up about nine
constant pressure on this defense to be in the right alignments
make the right calls Daniels on the fake pressure in his face
Those other on his car for a big game of more down the sideline
He goes there's a penalty flag and let's see what this is is Chris
Moore one of those subs playing with all these wide receiver injuries
Third and goal
Daniels looking throwing car touchdown Zach Gertz
Oh
Simple crossing route
Linebacker picks them up and then just kind of drops them,
but they're trying to spy Daniel.
So there's not much of a rush
And then earth just slips behind him.
No one sees them
Then more poor defense Murray
Just can't quite there
Daniels gonna keep it down
Excellent tackle from Geron black.
It looks like he was gonna walk right
in and so the conversion is no good
There you go.
I know you do I do
The Cowboys take over great field position
Prescott lusting it up George Pickett
What a catch
Oh
Second and 10 now here is Williams up the
got big scene for Williams inside the 30
He goes big note for Washington defensively
Aaron tells us during Armstrong big issue today.
No doubt
third and three
Can't wait for watch you on TV covering
that World Series KB looking forward to it
There's Aubrey from 47 away kick is up and
it is good from about 80. He is amazing
Third and six blitz is coming Daniel season high throw but
a great catch and short of the first down Robbie chosen
It was activated today for the commander
as the goal these injuries makes the catch
Get it for the fourth time press go a lot
of time airs it out deep down the field
No one home touchdown Dallas
Watch how early gets them to it's just a too high defense.
He's got to go here
He's here that entire middle of the fields
open CD throws his hand up like that.
Get it to me
Third long blitz picked up Daniels
far side throw complete and a good one
There is Robbie chosen again who just
got elevated from the practice squad
Third and nine blitz coming Daniels underneath long way to go
for chosen breaks a tackle dancing around and he stopped short
Second and 20 press got quick throw lay a pass a block CD
Springs his way out across the 40 a good
play gets past the original line of scrimmage
Troy's got a play call.
Here's doc pressure in his face in trouble.
It's here incomplete
excellent coverage that time
Daniels a throw in trouble steps away looks to run
Daniels racing outside around the 14 15 yard line
Third and five
Daniels
Can't find anyone now throws it deep he's got Lane wide open
There's a penalty flag on this route,
so let's see what it is,
but for now Jalen Lane hauls it in for a first down
Risk reward of that play there's not much risk,
but a great chance for a reward
Dan is again a lot of time looking around tells
people to go deep just gonna take off and then took up
After about a five-yard game from Shamar James
By clock at one
Barely get it off fourth down Daniels floats one in complete
Zach urts the attendant receiver there is a penalty at the
45 around the line though jumpstart this Cowboys run game
Which was invisible last year here's tap to throw outside.
He goes to lamb with a stiff arm and
Is brought down on the play by Morton
rush
Prescott over the middle comes it complete Ferguson first down Dallas
Third long commanders bail out of a blitz press got tipped again.
It's a rod pain
Third and 13
Daniels gets rid of it long way to go McNichols diving forward.
He's gonna be a little short
Yep, they're gonna mark him two yards short.
So it's fourth and two
Prescott first down CD lamb
Third long
Prescott pressure throws tight window incomplete that
was dangerous Mikey saying we're still was all over it
They got two timeouts remaining
Start out gets it out in the flat McNichols shoulder down looks
like he's got a first down that time is bland on the tackle
It's obviously a big drive for them only eight points in the
first quarter go a long way to put something on the board
Daniels in trouble steps away runs immediately
good run Daniels first down steps out of bounds
He saw the pressure took off and that one worked as he
picks up 14 two timeouts and they got Brandon Aubrey,
right?
So just make sure they don't touch it.
There's McNichols racing up the middle and he has got a first down
He's still on his feet
Looking for the end zone and shoved out of bounds around the one
What an effort by Jeremy McNichols first and goal for the commanders
Krosky merit back in the game and
running back after the big play from
Nichols damage gonna keep it and he is in for the touchdown
He's got Bill there.
Oh
And maybe in the Sun the glare coming through the windows
Wow
Get that ball back and with Aubrey.
There's nothing out of range
That's got some pressure he is sacked
Washington gets home
One time outlet for Dallas after the sack it's
Prescott launching going deep pickings.
How many great catches
is he gonna make today?
Unbelievable pickings up top for
44. This is what they're used to seeing.
He talked about a level
of trust that Dakka already amazing throw and catch.
Wow.
Now Dallas are gonna run with Williams.
He's home! Javante Williams!
Rumbling inside the five and he's finally taken down at the two.
13 seconds left they'll take a timeout I believe they do.
Can't run it these have to be throws at this point.
He will throw.
Prescott throws in the middle and it's
caught! Ferguson! Touchdown Dallas.
You know end up going down and giving him a touchdown.
A little chip.
Saynner still reacts late and that's his go-to guy.
And Joe Witt.
Yeah he's frustrated Tom right?
I mean.
Throw in to Daniels on the keeper.
Looking for an edge and boy he reached the ball.
They give it to him they do.
That reach gonna get him a first.
Daniels.
Looking.
Throw and caught for a first now.
It's Moore.
Chris Moore of the 44 yard reception earlier
comes back to help out his quarterback.
Good to move the trees on first and 10. Daniels.
The fake ball is loose!
Cowboys recover!
Just gets twisted up he's trying to get the
ball to urge there but it's kind of blanketed.
Ball gets knocked out of his hands and then
just twists it up by James on the tackle.
Kind of reaching for his right hamstring.
And again with the big knee brace on the left knee.
Yeah it's just.
Meanwhile the Cowboys golden opportunity
here with great field position.
On a second and two it is Williams.
What a cut! Oh my goodness to the outside! Make it blue!
Oh wow!
Devontae Williams.
What's coming?
Prescott sees it.
Corner and goes.
Pickens makes the catch for a first down.
Another one for George Pickens again on Latimore.
He could just deal with Dish.
Third down here.
Prescott looking to deal or maybe run.
Dax gonna lose his legs.
Close to a marker and now taking down right at it.
I think he's got it.
They don't want to get a chance to review that one.
Fake to Williams.
Prescott throws it out.
To Ferguson! Touchdown Dallas!
Ball they went fast and you got Savage in coverage.
And he just poor eye discipline so you kind
of rush to the line.
Yeah that's obviously looks like a
good sign for at least long term but
right now short term here's Mariota in the game for Washington.
He started twice this year on the
line.
He starts with a pretty good throw.
Moved to Jalen Lane in the sunshine for a first down.
Play clock and one.
They get it off.
Blitz is coming.
Mariota in trouble.
Being ripped away.
Stays alive.
Throws it in the track.
And he picked off! Guess who's around the lands?
One man to beat.
Pick six!
That was a pretty good place to be if you're a Dallas defender.
Sure is.
AWSAI how the NFL levels up the game.
Meanwhile gonna run it here with Mariota
with a nice run and a first down.
And then some.
It's finally shoved out of bounds.
Got a good block from Zach Ertz for Washington.
They get a first down on a fourth and eight.
Mariota on the keep.
Good run.
Mariota makes a climb.
That's an excellent run by Marcus Mariota down
right around the first down and in the game.
Give it to Rodriguez.
Stutter step.
Leading to the end zone.
Is he in?
No but it's a first and goal.
Let's see if it was.
Outstretched arm.
Now he's okay.
There's nothing there.
That is super tight.
He slide a credit card underneath that knee on that right side.
It's not there.
That's really close.
I mean I don't know if it's definitive which
they they ruled he was short on the field.
Well Dean you're busy right now.
So the penalty gives him a first down.
Jaden Blue in the game at tailback.
Prescott pressure.
Gets it outside.
Turpin makes a man miss.
Look out.
Turpin he's just so electric every time he gets the ball.
Alright third down.
Prescott gets it over to Lipki in the flat.
Has some room to go.
Lipki is stood up there by Alubu and Bobby Wagner.
Kick is up and it is perfect.
Like literally perfect.
Second and ten.
Mariota.
Irts is wide open.
Good catch in Ron Zachers into Dallas territory.
And there he goes all the way down to about the 42.
Pressure.
Mariota in trouble.
Mariota is dropped again.
It's Jadavia Clowney.
He has had a big night.
So here we go.
Commanders need it.
Fourth down and one.
Mariota on the fake.
Lofton has a man wide open.
Miss McCaffrey.
Oh man it was a Kimmy and instead the Cowboys take over.
Just going to run it to Williams down the side.
Into like 20 commanders.
And that's why it's been a frustrating start for the commanders.
Trying to look for a little room at the goal line.
And you get a tougher schedule and you're a
hunted team bringing you to this game today.
Glad you could join us today.
Two minutes to go.
The Cowboys are going to just wrap it up.
Jaden Blue has a first down and they could do the victory formation.
Offense is looking great.
And we'll come back and put the finishing touches here.
As Dak Prescott.
What a game.